tarladalal.com 2017-09-12

# TarlaDalal.com | Privacy Policy

At WWW.TARLADALAL.COM ( **“Website”** ), we encourage our users and registered members to interact with us as well as with each other. In the course of using or availing our Website, we may become privy to your personal information, including information that is of a confidential nature. We are committed in protecting the privacy and personal information of every such person who visits the Website. Your privacy is important to us and we strive to take reasonable care and protection of the personal information we receive from you.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy ( **"Policy"** ), as amended from time to time, is to give you an understanding on how we intend to collect and use the information you provide to us.

By using the Website and providing us such information, you hereby consent to the collection and use of such information for the purposes disclosed in this Policy.

### Personal Information

In order to access the Website or to become a member of he Website or to avail certain features of the Website, we may require certain information not limited to your age, gender, first and last name, birth date, title, zip code/pin code, occupation, industry, personal interests / hobbies, company or any other physical address, contact number, email or other contact information and other relevant data as may be required by us ( **"Personal Information"** ).

### Usage of Personal Information

We use your Personal Information to distinguish you from other users and to offer personalized services to you. We may use your Personal Information to:

  * seek your feedback or to contact you in relation to the products and services offered on the Website;
  * to process orders or applications submitted by you;
  * send you, from time to time, updates or advertisements;
  * anticipate and resolve problems related to our services;
  * allow you to subscribe to our newsletter/s;
  * verify your identity or to follow up with transactions initiated by you on the Website;
  * inform you of any changes to the Website, or to send you additional information about us or the Website;
  * respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * protect and defend the rights or property of Sanjay & Co. or the users of the Website;
  * to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Website or any policies thereof or as otherwise required by law;
  * transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with any company or entity;
  * administer or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement you have with us; and
  * allow you to enter promotions or sweepstakes, if any.

We may also remove all the personally identifiable information and use the rest for historical, statistical or scientific purposes.

### Comments

Sanjay & Co. may provide a facility of offering interactive forms and forums such as comments, blogs, discussion forums, etc on the Website. Any information that is disclosed in these forms and forums becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information.

Any recipes or other content, whether copyrightable or not, posted by any user or member of the Website will be public and viewable by all. 

You further acknowledge and agree that you are aware that any Personal Information you submit on the Website may be read, collected, copied, used or exploited by other users of the Website, including anonymous visitors.

### Non-Personal Information and its usage

We may also record and store the details, time and duration of your messages or requests and visits on the Website, including the domain name and the name of the web page from which you entered the Website or any web pages thereof, operating system and platform of your mobile device, pages viewed, information searched for or requested for and other relevant statistics and the options you select, each time you use the Website.

We will use such information for the purposes of improving the performance and operations of our Website and attract advertisers and listings for our Website.

### Authorization

You authorize us to exchange, share, part with all information (Personal and Non-Personal), across borders and from your country and jurisdiction to any other countries and jurisdictions across the world, with any agent, third party, or any service provider as may be required by law, customary practice, statistical analysis and verification or risk management and shall not hold us liable for use, storage or disclosure of this information.

### Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of every minor is especially important to us. The Website is not structured to attract minor children under eighteen (18) years. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 18 years.

### Third Party Websites

As a matter of convenience to you, Sanjay & Co. may contain links to other third party websites and advertisements. To provide the Website efficiently, we may share your information (Personal and Non-Personal) with certain third parties. The listing of an external website does not imply endorsement of such website by us. These third parties will be contractually bound to protect your information in accordance with our applicable privacy policies.

If you choose to visit any third party website through our Website, we shall not be responsible or liable for the privacy practices or any content or material of such third party websites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at such third party websites to confirm that you understand and agree with them.

### Advertising

We may use third party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit the Website. These companies may use your information about your visits to our Website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We may use cookies to serve such advertisements on the Website. 

### Use of Cookies

We may store some information such as cookies on your computer when you visit the Website. Cookies are small files that are stored on the hard drive of your computer ready for future access when you return to our Website. This information facilitates your use of the Website and ensures that you do not need to re-enter your details every time you visit it. You can erase or choose to block this information from your computer. The cookies do not contain or capture any personal information. You can configure your computer's browser to alert you when the Website is attempting to send you a cookie and allow you to accept or refuse the cookie. Your decision to refuse cookies will not prevent you from using the Website, but may limit your ability to take advantage of some of the advanced features of the Website. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests or for promotions or advertisements displayed on the Website. We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our Website. You may opt out of the use of the cookies by disabling cookies option in your web browser.

### Security

Sanjay & Co. has reasonable security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that it obtains from you, but Sanjay & Co. makes no assurances about its ability to prevent any such loss or misuse to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse or alteration.

### Access/Accuracy

To the extent that you provide us with your Personal Information, we wish to maintain your Personal Information complete, updated and accurate at all times. If you need to update or correct your Personal Information for any reason, you may update it yourself by logging at www.tarladalal.com. 

### Updates and Changes

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update or modify this Policy without any notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Website. It is your responsibility to review this Policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms. 

Upon updating the Policy, we will also revise the "Updated" date at the bottom of this Policy. 

### Contacting Us

We will address any questions, comments and concerns about our privacy policy and privacy practice. Please write to us at 

### Updated on April 11th 2012
